var QAList = [{
    question: "1. What does 'NaN' stand for in JavaScript? ",
    answers: {
        a: "A: Negative and Number",
        b: "B: Not a Number",
        c: "C: No Associated Number",
        d: "D: Never a Number"
    },
    correct: "b"
},
{
    question: "2. What does the modulus (%) operator return? ",
    answers: {
        a: "A: The remainder of a division",
        b: "B: Null",
        c: "C: false",
        d: "D: The sum of two numbers"
    },
    correct: "a"
},
{
    question: "3. How would you add 'n' to the end of an array? ",
    answers: {
        a: "A: array.append(n);",
        b: "B: array[n];",
        c: "C: array.push(n);",
        d: "D: n.push(array);"
    },
    correct: "c"
},
{
    question: "4. Which of the following is syntactically correct?",
    answers: {
        a: "A: for i = 0; i++; ",
        b: "B: for (i = 0; var i < 5; i++)",
        c: "C: for (var i = 0; i < 5; i++)",
        d: "D: for: i = 0, i < 5, i++"
    },
    correct: "c"
},
{
    question: "5. How would you create a new 'h1' element using JavaScript? ",
    answers: {
        a: "A: window.createEl('h1');",
        b: "B: document.create('<h1>')",
        c: "C: h1.createElement();",
        d: "D: document.createElement('h1');"
    },
    correct: "d"
},
{
    question: "6. Which of the following is not a datatype in JavaScript? ",
    answers: {
        a: "A: Number",
        b: "B: List",
        c: "C: Array",
        d: "D: Object"
    },
    correct: "b"
},
{
    question: "7. What does the following code represent `var arr = [ob{name: 'Bob'}];`? ",
    answers: {
        a: "A: An object containing an array",
        b: "B: An array containing an object",
        c: "C: A variable containing a string",
        d: "D: An object"
    },
    correct: "b"
},
{
    question: "8. Which is the proper way to declare a function in JavaScript? ",
    answers: {
        a: "A: function name(//code)",
        b: "B: name(args) {//code}",
        c: "C: fun name(args) {//code}",
        d: "D: function name(args) {//code}"
    },
    correct: "d"
},
{
    question: "9. How would you access the 3rd element in a JavaScript array? ",
    answers: {
        a: "A: array[3];",
        b: "B: array[2];",
        c: "C: array(3);",
        d: "D: array.access(3);"
    },
    correct: "b"
},
{
    question: "10. Given the array `var arr = [1, 4, 6, 7, 3];` What would `arr[4]` return? ",
    answers: {
        a: "A: 3",
        b: "B: 7",
        c: "C: 4",
        d: "D: None of the above"
    },
    correct: "a"
}
];
